Contact

MCloeteConsulting@gmail.com View my work

Marius Cloete UX Designer

About me

UX Skills



Competitor analysis User interviews User personas Task models Experience maps Information architecture Wireframing Prototyping Usability testing Preference testing Click testing Data analytics

I'm a UX designer with nearly 20 year's experience in the media industry which spans design, content creation, marketing, consumer research, audience measurement systems and marketing effectiveness. I was drawn to the field of UX because it presents a way to apply all of my cumulative experience in a creative, yet solution driven field. My background not only gives me a great understanding into what makes consumers tick, but provides me with excellent presentation and stakeholder management skills to guide organisations towards effective, consumer centred solutions.

Experience

Research Skills



Consumer behaviour Advertising effectiveness Depth interviews Marketing effectiveness Brand tracking Audience measurement Ethnography Social media listening

UX Designer, Journeez

May 2017 - Present

Research Consultant, Magnetic Media June 2015 - May 2017

International Effectiveness Specialist, Clear Channel Outdoor June 2014 - May 2015

Head of Research, PPA

May 2010 - May 2014

Consumer Insight Manager, Evening Standard March 2006 - April 2010

General Manager Marketing, Mail & Guardian October 2000 - September 2005

More information available on request

Soft skills



Stakeholder management Supplier management Excellent presenter Line management Copywriting Influencing

Education

CareerFoundry

UX Design & Research

Vaal University

B.Tech Cost & Management Accounting

Tools •



InVision Photoshop Illustator InDesign

Personal

Dual British & South African Citizen